[{
    "level": 1,
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "1 + 1 = ?",
            "correct_answer": 2,
            "wrong_answers": [0, 1]
        },
        {
            "question": "10 + 12 = ?",
            "correct_answer": 22,
            "wrong_answers": [12, 2]
        },
        {
            "question": "5 - 5 = ?",
            "correct_answer": 0,
            "wrong_answers": [10, -5]
        },
        {
            "question": "4 - 3 = ?",
            "correct_answer": 1,
            "wrong_answers": [7, 8]
        },
        {
            "question": "7 + 10 = ?",
            "correct_answer": 17,
            "wrong_answers": [-3, 10]
        },
        {
            "question": "8 + 2 = ?",
            "correct_answer": 10,
            "wrong_answers": [82, 28]
        },
        {
            "question": "10/2 = ?",
            "correct_answer": 5,
            "wrong_answers": [20, 12]
        },
        {
            "question": "10 + 20 = ?",
            "correct_answer": 30,
            "wrong_answers": [300, 120]
        },
        {
            "question": "50 - 30 = ?",
            "correct_answer": 20,
            "wrong_answers": [30, 80]
        },
        {
            "question": " (1 + 10) - 6 = ?",
            "correct_answer": 5,
            "wrong_answers": [-3, 17]
        }
    ]
},{
    "level": 2,
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "20 - 7 = ?",
            "correct_answer": 13,
            "wrong_answers": [12, 15]
        },
        {
            "question": "3 - 5 = ?",
            "correct_answer": -2,
            "wrong_answers": [2, 3]
        },
        {
            "question": "10 - 4 = ?",
            "correct_answer": 6,
            "wrong_answers": [4, 8]
        },
        {
            "question": "24 - 6 = ?",
            "correct_answer": 18,
            "wrong_answers": [19, 16]
        },
        {
            "question": "30 - 25 = ?",
            "correct_answer": 5,
            "wrong_answers": [-5, 55]
        },
        {
            "question": "9 + 5 = ?",
            "correct_answer": 14,
            "wrong_answers": [15, 41]
        },
        {
            "question": "9 + 21 = ?",
            "correct_answer": 30,
            "wrong_answers": [40, 20]
        },
        {
            "question": "5 x 6 = ?",
            "correct_answer": 30,
            "wrong_answers": [36, 56]
        },
        {
            "question": " ((9 + 11) - 12) + 8 = ?",
            "correct_answer": 16,
            "wrong_answers": [8, 14]
        }
    ]
},{
    "level": 3,
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "1001 - 8 = ?",
            "correct_answer": 993,
            "wrong_answers": [800, 8000]
        },
        {
            "question": "5 - 6 = ?",
            "correct_answer": -1,
            "wrong_answers": [0, 2]
        },
        {
            "question": "80 - 63 = ?",
            "correct_answer": 17,
            "wrong_answers": [50, 140]
        },
        {
            "question": "6 - 0 = ?",
            "correct_answer": 6,
            "wrong_answers": [600, 0]
        },
        {
            "question": "7 + 7 = ?",
            "correct_answer": 14,
            "wrong_answers": [77, 7]
        },
        {
            "question": "3/6 = ?",
            "correct_answer": 0.5,
            "wrong_answers": [3, 2.5]
        },
        {
            "question": "(3x9)/2 = ?",
            "correct_answer": 13.5,
            "wrong_answers": [14, "None of the above"]
        },
        {
            "question": "9 + 5 - 12 + 8 = ?",
            "correct_answer": 10,
            "wrong_answers": [9, "None of the above"]
        },
        {
            "question": " 8 x 9 = ?",
            "correct_answer": 72,
            "wrong_answers": [89, 76]
        },
        {
            "question": "  (12/3) x 8 = ?",
            "correct_answer": 32,
            "wrong_answers": [48, 4.44444]
        }
    ]
}]